https://www.wilsonagri.co.uk/legals/

Skip to content
Legals
The following are terms of a legal agreement between you and Wilson Agri. By accessing, browsing and/or using this website, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree, to be bound by these terms and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including export and re-export control laws and regulations. If you do not agree to these terms, do not use this website.About usThis website is controlled and operated by Wilson Agri (referred to in these terms of use as “Wilson Agri”, “we”, “us” or “our”). Wilson Agri is a limited liability company registered in Northern Ireland. Our registered office address is: Wilson Agriculture, 75 Drumcroone Road, Coleraine, Northern Ireland, BT51 4ED, Northern Ireland and our VAT number is: GB254128768.How to contact usYou can contact us by email at info@wilsonagri.co.uk if you have any questions, comments or complaints about this website.Changes to these terms of useWe keep these terms of use under review and will place any updates on this webpage. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the website and your continued access, browsing or other use of the website constitutes your agreement to all such terms of use. These terms of use were last updated on 25th Jan 2012Access to and use of the websiteWe are the owner or the licensee of all intellectual property rights in this website and the material on it (including all text, trade marks, data, graphics, layout, logos, images, music or other audio material, clips, films or other moving images, algorithms, product details and/or software published or otherwise available on the website from time to time).Subject to these terms of use, we grant you a limited, temporary, revocable and non-exclusive licence to access, browse and use this website for your personal and non commercial use only. You may print off one copy of any page(s) from this website for your personal reference.Except as set out in the limited licence above (or as required under any applicable law), no part of this website may be used, reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, accessed, modified, or otherwise exploited, in full or in part, for any purpose without our prior written consent. In particular, you are not permitted to republish any part of this website on another website, in any other medium (print, electronic or otherwise) or as part of any commercial service without our prior written permission. All the intellectual property rights referred to above remain owned by us or our licensors.Acceptable use of the websiteWhile accessing, browsing and/or using this website you must:(a) comply with all applicable laws, regulations and codes;(b) not link to any part of the website other than the homepage;(c) not frame or use framing techniques to enclose the website, or any part of the website, without our prior written consent;(d) not modify, or attempt to modify, all or any part of the content on the website; and/or(e) not gain or attempt to gain unauthorised access to the website, the server on which the website is stored or any third party server, computer or database connected to the website.Whilst you may link to the homepage of this website, you must only do so in a way that is fair, does not harm our reputation and does not suggest any form of association, approval or endorsement of you, your goods or services and/or your website by Wilson AgriTermination or suspension of your access to the websiteAt any time and without giving you any advance notice, we may permanently or temporarily and for any reason:(a) terminate, suspend or deny your access to this website (whether in whole or in part);(b) terminate your permission to link to this website; and/or(c) remove or edit any content on the website, andin such circumstances all our liability (as well as the liability of our directors, employees or other representatives) for any loss whatsoever arising from our removing or editing content and/or your limited use of or inability to use this website (either in whole or in part) is excluded, insofar as it is possible to do so in law.Third party linksThis website may contain links to third party websites. We are not responsible for, nor do we endorse in any way such third party websites or their content. If you decide to access any of the third party websites linked to this website, you do so entirely at your own risk.DisclaimerAll information and/or data on this website is provided on an “as is” basis. To the extent permitted by law, all conditions, warranties and other terms which might otherwise by implied are now expressly excluded and no representations, warranties or terms of any kind are made in respect of the website or the content, including, without limitation, warranties of satisfactory quality, accuracy, adequacy, conformity to description or fitness for any particular purpose.Neither we nor any of our data providers or affiliates gives any warranty or guarantee: (a) relating to the availability of the website; or (b) that the website and/or our operation of it, the content or the server that makes the website available, are error or virus free or free of other harmful components; or (c) that your use of this website will be uninterrupted.Limitation of liabilityNothing in these terms of use excludes or limits our liability for:(a) death or personal injury caused by our negligence or that of any of our officers, employees or agents; or(b) fraudulent misrepresentation; or(c) any liability which it is not lawful to exclude either now or in the future.Subject to the above, we will not be liable, whether in tort (including for negligence or breach of statutory duty), contract or otherwise, for: (a) any loss or damage which may arise from reliance on any information contained on this website; (b) any loss, damage or costs suffered or incurred by you arising from viruses or other harmful components received via this website; or (c) any loss of profits; loss of business; depletion of goodwill or similar losses; loss of anticipated savings; loss of contracts; loss of use; loss or corruption of data or information; or any special, indirect, consequential or pure economic loss incurred by any user in connection with this website.EnforcementIf the whole or any part of any provision of these terms of use is or becomes invalid, void or unenforceable for any reason the same shall to the extent required be severed from these terms of use and rendered ineffective so far as is possible without modifying the remaining provisions of these terms of use and shall in no way affect the validity or enforceability of any other provisions.WaiverNo waiver by us of any breach of these terms of use shall constitute a waiver of any other prior or subsequent breach and we shall not be affected by any delay, failure or omission to enforce or express forbearance granted in respect of any of your obligations.Governing law and jurisdictionThese terms of use and/or your use of the website shall be governed by and construed in accordance with Northern Irish law and the Northern Irish courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute whichmay arise.Privacy and data protectionThis website is controlled and operated by Wilson Agri (referred to in this privacy policy as “Wilson Agri”, “we”, “us” or “our”). This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.What information we collect and how we collect itIf we collect any personal information through our website we will explain what we intend to do with it.We use third party analytical tools (such as Google Analytics) to analyse how our website is being used. These tools use “cookies” (small text files placed on your computer) to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form.The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to third party service providers such as Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.We will not use the analytical tools to track or to collect any personally identifiable information from you and we will not associate any data gathered from this website with any personally identifying information from any source as part of our use of the analytical tools.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their privacy policies.Your rightsYou have the right to request a copy of any personal information that we hold about you. To obtain a copy of this personal information, please write to us at the address set out below. We may charge a small fee forthis service.If we do hold information about you, you may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.Changes to our privacy policyWe keep our privacy policy under review and we will place any updates on this webpage. This privacy policy was last updated on 25th January 2011.How to contact usIf you have any questions about our privacy policy or personal information we hold about you, please contact us by post at the following address:Legal DepartmentWilson Agriculture75 Drumcroone RoadColeraineNorthern IrelandBT51 4ED
Get In Touch
Call Us
+44 (0) 2870 868430
Request a Brochure
Book a Demonstration
Get In TouchT: +44 (0) 2870 868430F: +44 (0) 2870 868803E: info@wilsonagri.co.uk
AddressHead OfficeWilson Agri75 Drumcroone RoadColeraineBT51 4EDNorthern Ireland
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
